National Arts Club
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Scrapbooks, 1898-1940, Series 9:
  - Clippings, 1912-1940, 9.3:
    - Volume 17, 1936-1940 (Reel 4268, Frame 660-935)
Apr.-May, 1906 Exhibition by the Women's Art Club of New York
Nov. 8-18 s, 1906 Opening Exhibition [first exhibition in new quarters]: American Paintings from the Collection of Mr. William T. Evans (D45:29-34, and volume 4)
Dec., 1906 Books of the Year
Dec. 8-Jan. 1 s, 1906 Pictures by Some American Painters (volume 4)
Jan. 12-Feb. 1 s, 1907 Modern German Paintings from the Collection of Mr. Hugo Reisinger (N443:716-717, and volume 4)
Feb. s, 1907 Exhibition of Wood Engravings by Timothy Cole made for Century Magazine
Feb., 1907 Longfellow Memorial
Mar. 13-31, 1907 Sixth Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr., 1907 New York Society of Ceramic Artists
Apr., 1907 Paintings and Sculpture by Members
May s, 1907 Exhibition of Artists' Preliminary Sketches
May-Nov., 1907 Sketches by Members
Oct. 16-Nov. 16 s, 1907 Fall Exhibition of Sketches by Members (volume 4)
Nov. 20-Dec. 11, 1907 Arts and Crafts Exhibition (N29:1001-1026)
Dec., 1907 Second Annual Exhibition of the New Books of the Year
Jan. 4-25 s, 1908 Contemporary Art (N443:744-746, and volume 5)
Feb., 1908 First Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art
Feb. 1-15 s, 1908 Contemporary Paintings (volume 5)
Mar., 1908 Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr. 2-25 * s, 1908 Special Exhibition of Members' Work (volume 5)
Apr. 15-May 8 s, 1908 Members' Spring Exhibition (volume 5)
Apr. 25-May 15 s, 1908 Paintings Loaned by C. C. Ruthrauff (volume 5)
May *, 1908 Exhibition of Painting, Sculpture, and Illustration under the auspices of the Art Students League of New York
Oct. 21-Nov. 7 s, 1908 Members' Fall Sketch Exhibition (volume 5)
Nov. *, 1908 Third Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec., 1908 Arts and Crafts Exhibition
Jan., 1909 Second Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art
Jan., 1909 Small Exhibition of Paintings and Drawings by Contemporary Artists
Feb. 2-20 s, 1909 International Exhibition of Pictorial Photography (volume 1)
Feb. 23-Mar. 17 s, 1909 John W. Alexander Retrospective Exhibition (volume 5)
Apr., 1909 Exhibition of the New York Society of Keramic Arts
May, 1909 Spring Exhibition of Members' Work
July, 1909 Paintings from the Collection of Mr. and Mrs. William T. Evans
Sept.-Oct., 1909 Three Centuries of New York, under the auspices of the Hudson-Fulton Celebration
Nov. 3-26 s, 1909 Fourth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year (volume 5)
Dec., 1909 Third Annual Exhibition of Arts and Crafts
Jan., 1910 William M. Chase Retrospective Exhibition
Feb., 1910 Exhibition of American Landscape Painting
Mar. 2-28 s, 1910 Exhibition of Paintings by Louis Mark, of Budapest (volume 5)
Apr. 6-30 s, 1910 Exhibition of Paintings by Alfred East, of London (N134:465-469, and volume 5)
May, 1910 Exhibition of Household Art, under the auspices of the Domestic Training Department of the Public Schools
May 4-Oct. s, 1910 Third Annual Exhibition of the Former Students of the Art Students League (volume 5)
Oct. 20-Nov. 1 s +, 1910 Third Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art (volume 5)
Nov.-Dec., 1910 Fifth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. * +, 1910 Fourth Annual Arts and Crafts Exhibition
Jan. 5-Feb. 3 s +, 1911 First Annual Artist Life Members' Exhibition (volume 5)
Feb. +, 1911 Exhibition of the New York Society of Keramic Arts
Feb. 11-Mar. 10, 1911 Circuit Exhibition of Contemporary Art (D12:437-439; N52:105-107)
Mar. 8-Apr. 5 * s +, 1911 Paintings and Drawings by Walter Shirlaw, N.A. (N52:967-973, and volume 5)
Apr., 1911 Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr. 26-May * s +, 1911 Group Exhibition of Paintings: William R. Derrick, Reynolds Beal, Frederick J. Waugh (volume 5)
Oct. 25-Nov. 4 * +, 1911 Exhibition of Color Schemes and Model Rooms in Miniature
Nov. 8-30 * +, 1911 Sixth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-28 * +, 1911 Fifth Annual Arts and Crafts Exhibition
Jan. 3-28 s +, 1912 First Prize Exhibition of Artist Life Members (N443:754-756, and volume 6)
Jan. 31-Feb. 18 * s +, 1912 Otto Walter Beck Exhibition (volume 6)
Feb. 21-Mar. 10 s +, 1912 Etchings of E. T. Hurley (volume 6)
Mar. 13-20 s +, 1912 National Park Pictures Collected and Exhibited by the Department of the Interior (volume 3)
Apr. 4-21 s +, 1912 Paintings, Embroideries, and Tapestries from the Collection of Mr. Emerson McMillan (D45:462-468; N443:757-762, and volume 6)
Apr. 4-Mar. 12 s, 1912 Exhibition of Original Dickens and Thackeray Drawings by Harry Furniss (volume 3)
May 8-June 1 * s +, 1912 Sculpture Exhibition (volume 6)
June 4-8 +, 1912 Exhibition of Industrial Art, under the auspices of The School Art League and the Art Departments of the City High Schools
June-Oct., 1912 Summer Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Oct. 16-Nov. 12 +, 1912 Third Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators
Nov. 13-29, 1912 Seventh Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 4-28 +, 1912 Sixth Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 8-Feb. 9 +, 1913 Work of the Painter, Sculptor, and Architect Members (N443:763-767; N50:126-130)
Feb. 12-Mar. 9 * +, 1913 Exhibition of Works by the Late Frederick Warren Freer
Mar. 12-31 +, 1913 The Applied Arts of Germany
Apr. 2-27 +, 1913 Small Works by Six Painters: Richard E. Miller, Frederick Carl Frieseke, Charles W. Hawthorne, William Wendt, William Ritschel, and Elise Dodge Pattee
Apr. 30-June 1 +, 1913 Small Marbles and Bronzes (N551:732-737)
May-June, 1913 Summer Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture
Oct. 15-Nov. 9, 1913 Society of Illustrators
Nov. 12-28, 1913 Eighth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 3-28 * +, 1913 Seventh Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 8-Feb. 1 +, 1914 Work of Painter, Sculptor, and Architect Members
Feb. 4-21, 1914 The Pastellists
Feb. 5-Mar. 21 x +, 1914 Contemporary Art
Mar. 11-29 * +, 1914 Hungarian Peasant Art (N134:470-479)
Apr. 1-May 2 +, 1914 Paintings by Eleven Western Artists
May 6-31 * +, 1914 Exhibition of Small Sculpture (N551:738-743)
June-Sept., 1914 Paintings
Nov. 4-27, 1914 Ninth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 3-28 +, 1914 Eighth Annual Exhibition of National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 7-31 +, 1915 Work of Painter Members (N551:744-746)
Feb. 4-25 +, 1915 Forty-eighth Annual Exhibition of American Water Color Society
Mar. 3-24 +, 1915 Portraits (N551:747-748)
Apr. 7-13 +, 1915 Sculpture
May 5-21, 1915 Exhibition of Municipal Art Society
June-Oct. *, 1915 Work of Painter Members
Oct. 13-30 +, 1915 Fifth Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators
Nov. 5-13 +, 1915 American Wood Engraving, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts
Nov. 17-Dec. 3, 1915 Tenth Anniversary Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 8-30 +, 1915 Ninth Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 6-28 +, 1916 Work of Painter Members
Feb. 3-27 +, 1916 Forty-ninth Annual Exhibition of American Water Color Society
Mar. 2-25 * +, 1916 Loan Exhibition of Portraits of Academicians and Associates Selected from the Permanent Collection of the National Academy of Design (N551:749-752; N134:480-483)
Mar. 28-Apr. 14 +, 1916 One Hundred American Paintings by the American Institute of Graphic Arts (N443:768-770)
Mar. 28-Apr. 14 +, 1916 Exhibition of American Printing
Apr. 19-May 6, 1916 Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society
May 10-26, 1916 English Posters
June-Aug. +, 1916 Members' Summer Sketch Exhibition
Oct. 5-Nov. 3, 1916 Photography, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts
Nov. 9-30, 1916 Eleventh Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-29, 1916 Tenth Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 3-28 +, 1917 Annual Exhibition of the Work of Artist Members
Feb. 1-24 +, 1917 Fiftieth Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Feb. 28-Mar. 23 +, 1917 Etchings, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts
Mar. 29-Apr. 27, 1917 Paintings by Boston Artists
May 2-Sept. +, 1917 Members' Sketch Exhibition
Oct. 3-31 +, 1917 Paintings from the Netherlands Section of the Panama-Pacific Exposition
Oct. 4-31, 1917 Illustrations of the Catskill Aqueduct
Nov. 8-30 +, 1917 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 6-29, 1917 Eleventh Annual Exhibition of the National Society of Craftsmen
Jan. 3-Feb. 1 +, 1918 Annual Exhibition of Paintings by Members
Feb. 7-Mar. 1 +, 1918 Fifty-first Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Mar. 20-Apr. 26, 1918 Life Membership Pictures from the Permanent Collection
May, 1918 War Posters, under the auspices of the American Society of Graphic Arts
June 2-Oct. 1 +, 1918 Sketch Exhibition by Members
Dec. 5-28 +, 1918 Twelfth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Jan. 8-31 +, 1919 Retrospective Exhibition of the Work of the Artist Life Members
Feb., 1919 Fifty-second Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Mar., 1919 Exhibition of War Housing
Apr. 2-May 3 +, 1919 Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators (N29:873-875)
May-Oct. +, 1919 Annual Exhibition of Sketches by Members
Nov., 1919 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Jan. 7-30 +, 1920 Annual Exhibition of Painter and Sculptor Members (N29:864-866)
Feb., 1920 Fifty-third Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society
Mar., 1920 Drawings from Artists' Portfolios
Mar. 3-27 x +, 1920 American Drawings and Sculpture Sketches
Mar. 31-Apr. 16 +, 1920 Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators (N29:867-869)
May, 1920 Printing by the American Institute of Graphic Arts
June-Oct. +, 1920 Sketches and Small Sculpture by Members
Nov., 1920 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 1-29 +, 1920 Exhibition of Art Expression by Club Members
Jan. 5-27 +, 1921 Members' Annual Prize Exhibition
Mar. 2-31 +, 1921 Art Directors Club First Annual Exhibition of Drawings and Paintings Used in American Advertising
Apr. 7-30, 1921 Exhibition of Old Prints, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts (N443:775-778)
May-Oct., 1921 Pictures from the Club's Permanent Collection
Nov., 1921 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-30 +, 1921 Humorists Exhibition
Jan. 5-28 +, 1922 Members' Annual Prize Exhibition
Feb., 1922 Seventh Annual Exhibition of Contemporary Bookplates, held by the American Bookplate Society
Feb. 15-Mar. 5 +, 1922 Exhibition of Paintings by Charles C.Curran, Franklin de Haven, George Glenn Newell, Harry W. Watrous
Mar., 1922 Lithographs
Apr. 5-30 +, 1922 Loan Exhibition of American Painting and Sculpture Owned by Club Members
May-Oct. +, 1922 Summer Exhibition of Artist Members
Nov., 1922 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 6-29 +, 1922 Work by Members
Jan. 10-Feb. 10 +, 1923 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Feb. 14-Mar. 3 +, 1923 Humorists Exhibition
Mar., 1923 Craftwork from Berea College, Kentucky
Mar., 1923 Group Exhibition: Roy Brown, Oscar Fehrer, Edmund Greacen, Eugene Higgins, Lee Laurie, F. Luis Mora, Carl Rungius, Edward C. Volkert.
Mar. 28-Apr. 20 +, 1923 Group Exhibition: Leon Dabo, William R. Derrick, Charles P. Gruppe, Hayley Lever, Charles R. Patterson
Apr., 1923 Miniature Garden Exhibition, by the Garden Club of America
May-July, 1923 Exhibition Selected from the Permanent Collection
June 5-28 +, 1923 Annual Prize Exhibition of Painter and Sculptor Members
Nov., 1923 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 12-29 +, 1923 Work of Living American Etchers
Jan. 9-Feb. 2 +, 1924 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Mar. 5-29 +, 1924 Exhibition of Sculpture
Apr., 1924 Selected Paintings from the Permanent Collection
Apr. 30-May 15 +, 1924 Exhibition of Books Illustrating the History of Printing
June, 1924 Adirondack Mountain Club Exhibition of Photographs
Nov. *, 1924 Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 10-27 +, 1924 Second Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers
Jan. 7-31 +, 1925 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture (N552:122-159)
Feb. 23-Mar. 7 +, 1925 Autograph Letters with Accompanying Portraits of Authors, Statesmen, Artists, etc.
Apr. 8-May 9 +, 1925 Exhibition of Lithographs, Wood Blocks, and Linoleum Cuts
Nov., 1925 Twentieth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 3-20, 1925 Work of Living American Etchers (N552:1-7)
Jan. 13-Feb. 6 +, 1926 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture (N552:19-21)
Feb. 10-27 +, 1926 Group Exhibiton by Members of the National Arts Club
Mar. 3-27 +, 1926 Copies of Old Masters
Apr., 1926 Architecture, Sculpture, and Decorative Painting
May +, 1926 Fifth International Exhibition of the Brooklyn Society of Etchers (N552:34-48)
Summer +, 1926 Summer Exhibition
Aug.-Oct. x, 1926 The Vollbehr Incunabula Exhibition
Nov., 1926 Twenty-first Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 2-22 +, 1926 Fourth Annual Exhibition of Works of Living American Etchers (N552:8-12)
Jan. 5-29 +, 1927 Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members
Feb. 11-27 +, 1927 Exhibition and Auction of Works of Art by Artist Members
Mar. 2-21 +, 1927 Invited Exhibition by Distinguished American Painters (NHS4:693-695)
Apr. 6-29 +, 1927 Norse Pictorial Weaving--Mrs. Berthea Aske Bergh (N552:66-68)
Nov., 1927 Twenty-second Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 7-24 +, 1927 Fifth Annual Exhibition of Works of Living American Etchers (N552:13-18)
Jan., 1928 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Feb. 8-29 +, 1928 Small Paintings
Mar. 8-31 x, 1928 Exhibition of Decorative Arts
Apr. 4-20 +, 1928 Exhibition by Junior Artist Members of the Club
Nov., 1928 Twenty-third Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec., 1928 Small Paintings
Jan. 8-Feb. 8 + Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Feb. 13-Mar. 8 Sixth Annual Exhibition by Living American Etchers
Mar. + Richard M. Hurd Loan Exhibition of Italian Primitives
Apr. 3-26 + Exhibition by Junior Artist Members of the Club
May 1-Oct. 1 + Summer Exhibition by Painter Life Members
Nov. Twenty-fourth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 4-26 * + Exhibition of the Decorative Arts
Jan. 8-Feb. 1 +, 1930 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Feb. 5-28 x +, 1930 Seventh Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers
Mar. 5-28 +, 1930 Junior Artist Members' Exhibition
Apr. 16-Sept. 30 +, 1930 Members' Exhibition of Small Paintings (N134:484-490)
Nov., 1930 Silver Anniversary Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 3-26 * +, 1930 Eighth Annual Exhibition by Living American Etchers
Jan. 7-Feb. 6 +, 1931 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Mar. 4-27 +, 1931 Exhibition by the Junior Artist Members
Mar. 13-Apr. 15 x, 1931 Auction Exhibition and Sale by Artist Members
Apr. 1-25 +, 1931 Members' Work of the New York Water Color Club
May 2-24 +, 1931 The Story of Gramercy Park in Portraits and Historical Objects of the Period, in connection with Gramercy Park Centenary Celebration
June 3-Oct. 1 +, 1931 Members' Exhibition of Small Paintings
Oct. 21-Nov. 20, 1931 Twenty-sixth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Nov. 26-Dec. 26, 1931 Sixteenth Annual Exhibition by the Society of American Etchers (formerly The Brooklyn Society of Etchers)
Jan. 6-13 +, 1932 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Feb. 3-27 +, 1932 Exhibition of Drawings by Artist Members
Mar. 2-26 +, 1932 Paintings by Junior Artist Members
Mar. 13-Apr. 15 +, 1932 Auction Exhibition and Sale by Artist Members
Apr. 20-30 +, 1932 Exhibition by a Group of New York Art Schools
May 4-Oct. 1 +, 1932 Members' Annual Exhibition of Small Paintings
Jan. 4-27 +, 1933 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Mar. 1-31 +, 1933 Junior Artist Members
Apr. 5-22 +, 1933 Society of Illustrators
May 3-Oct. 1 +, 1933 Members' Exhibition of Small Paintings and Sculpture
Jan. 3-27 +, 1934 Members' Annual Exhibition
Jan. 31-Mar. 2 +, 1934 Memorial Exhibition of a Group of Former Painter and Sculptor Members: Max Bohm, Emil Carlsen, Charles Hawthorne, Robert Henri, Karl Bitter, Solon Borglum, Daniel Chester French, Edmund Quinn
Mar. 7-29 +, 1934 Junior Artist Members
Apr. 4-27 +, 1934 Society of Illustrators, Thirty-second Annual Exhibition
May 2-June 28 +, 1934 Members' Exhibition of Small Paintings and Sculpture (N552:69-71; N134:491-494)
Nov.-Dec., 1934 Seventeenth Annual Exhibition of the Society of American Etchers (formerly The Brooklyn Society of Etchers) (N552:49-65)
undated Twenty-ninth Annual Exhibition of Fifty Books of the Year
Jan. 9-Feb. 1 +, 1935 Members' Exhibition (N552:22-24)
Feb. 6-Mar. 2 +, 1935 Members' No Jury Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture (N552:72-74)
Mar. 6-29 +, 1935 Junior Artist Members (N552:75-77)
Apr. 3-27 +, 1935 Loan Exhibition of Works of Art owned by Artist Members (N552:84-96)
undated Thirtieth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
undated Twentieth Annual Exhibition of the Society of American Etchers
Jan. 8-31 +, 1936 Members' Annual Exhibition (M552:25-27)
Mar. 4-27 +, 1936 Junior Artist Members (N552:78-80)
Apr. 1-May 1 x +, 1936 Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations (N552:92-94)
Spring +, 1936 First Annual Exhibition of Pictorial Photography by the Pictorial Forum (N552:87-91)
1936 Thirty-first Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
undated Twenty-first Annual Exhibition of the Society of American Etchers
Jan. 6-29 +, 1937 Members' Annual Exhibition
Mar. 3-26 +, 1937 Exhibition by the Younger Artists Group (N134:495-497)
Mar. 31-Apr. 27 +, 1937 Second Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations (N552:95-97)
Nov. *, 1937 Thirty-second Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year
Dec. 8-25 +, 1937 Members' Exhibition of Smaller Paintings and Black and Whites (N552:110-112)
Jan. 12-27, 1938 Exhibition of Former Painter and Sculptor Members (N552:113-115)
Mar. 14-Apr. 2 +, 1938 Third Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations (N552:98-100)
Apr. 6-20 +, 1938 Younger Artists Group Exhibition (N552:107-109)
Jan. 12-27 x +, 1939 Memorial Exhibition of the Work of a Group of Former Painter and Sculptor Members (N134:498-499)
Feb. 1-25 +, 1939 Members' Exhibition (N552:28-30)
Mar. 1-31 +, 1939 Exhibition of Flower Paintings (N552:116-118; N134:500-502)
Mar. 3-26, 1939 Younger Artists Group (N552:104-106)
Apr. 5-21 +, 1939 Fourth Annual Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations (N552:101-103)
May 10-24 +, 1939 Annual Junior Members' Exhibition (N552:81-83; N134:503-505)
June-Oct. +, 1939 Selected Works by Deceased Artists from the National Arts Club Permanent Collection (N552:119-121; N134:506-508)
Oct. 18-28 +, 1939 Special Exhibition of Paintings by Junior Members
Dec. 4-25 +, 1939 Christmas Sale of Paintings, Drawings, Photographs, and Sculpture by Junior Members
Jan. 3-19 +, 1940 Members' Annual Exhibition
Jan. 24-Feb. 9 +, 1940 Distinguished Exhibition of the Work of Living American Painters, Non-Members
Feb. 14-29 +, 1940 Exhibition and Sale of Ceramics (N134:511-513)
Mar. 19-29, 1940 Fontainebleau Alumni Exhibition
Apr. 3-19 +, 1940 Annual Junior Members' Exhibition
Apr. 24-May 3 +, 1940 Flower and Still Life Paintings
May 8-June 1, 1940 Special Exhibition of Water Colors, Architectural Renderings, Type Compositions, and Color Reproductions by Edwin Hooper Denby, A.I.A., S.A.D.G. (N443:779-780; N134:509-510)
Dec. +, 1940 Twenty-fifth Annual Exhibition of the Society of American Etchers
Feb. 4-Mar. 1, 1942 Exhibition of Paintings by Artists of the United Nations (N134:512-518)
June 12-Sept. 30, 1942 Members' Summer Exhibition (N134:519)
Dec. 16-Jan. 22, 1942 Exhibition of Chinese and Indian Art (N134:520)
Mar. 31-, 1943 Exhibition of Junior Members (N134:521)
July 1-Sept. 30, 1943 Summer Exhibition of Smaller Paintings by Members (N134:522)
Feb. 17-Mar. 15, 1944 Exhibition of Studies by American Masters (N134:523)
Oct. 5-27, 1944 Exhibition of Enlarged Photographs of American Patriots as Seen in Sculpture (N134:523)
Jan. 10-Feb. 9 x, 1945 Members' Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Dec. 22-Jan. 4, 1945 Seventh Annual Exhibition of the American Veterans Society of Artists, Inc. (N134:527-540)
May 21-30, 1946 The Traphagen School Exhibition of Costume Design, Illustrating the Development of American Fashion (N134:526)
Feb. 20-Mar. 7, 1947 Exhibition of Contemporary Chinese Paintings (N134:541)
Apr. 20-May 2, 1947 Junior Members' Exhibition
Dec. 10-24, 1947 Ninth Annual Exhibition of American Veterans Society of Artists, Inc. (N121:721-733)
Feb. 23-Mar. 6, 1948 Forty-seventh Annual Exhibition of the New York Society of Ceramic Arts (N134:543)
Mar. 9-21, 1948 Annual Exhibition of Junior Members (N134:543)
Apr. 8-May 30, 1948 Fiftieth Anniversary Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members, Past and Present (N134:543)
June 10-Sept., 1948 Members' Summer Exhibition (N134:544)
Jan. 19-Feb. 9, 1949 Fifty-first Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists (N134:544)
Mar. 14-31, 1949 Exhibition by Members of the Federation of Modern Painters and Sculptors (N134:545)
May 5-Sept. 15, 1949 Members' Summer Exhibition (N134:546)
Oct. 15-Nov. 4, 1949 Fourth Annual Exhibition of the Photo-Engravers Society
Jan. 4-Feb. 1, 1950 Fifty-second Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists (N134:546-548 and 550)
Jan. 28-Feb. 19, 1950 Eighty-third Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society (N134:549)
Feb. 8-23, 1950 Exhibition of Creative Art Associates (N134:549)
Mar. 16-Apr. 2, 1950 Exhibition of Room Interiors Especially Designed by Members of the American Institute of Decorators, in collaboration with Members of the National Society of Mural Painters (N134:551)
May 7-28, 1950 Active Members' Exhibition (N134:551-554)
June 28-Sept. 15, 1950 Members' Summer Exhibition (N134:555)
Feb. 26-Mar. 17 x, 1951 Paul Mommen
Mar. 24-Apr. 19, 1951 Exhibition of Paintings by Non-Members (N134:558-559)
May 5-31, 1951 Spring Water Color Exhibition (N134:560)
June 6-, 1951 Group Exhibition by Distinguished Artist Members: Gifford Beal, Louis Betts, Charles Clapman, Walter Farndon, Albert Groll, Eugene Higgins, Leon Kroll, Van Dearing Perrine, Keith Shaw Williams
Jan. 6-30, 1952 Fifty-fourth Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists (D176:917-919; N134:561)
Feb. 9-28, 1952 Annual Water Color Exhibition (N134:562)
Mar. 9-27, 1952 Exhibition of Oil Paintings by Distinguished American Artists (N134:572)
Jan. 4-18, 1953 Fifty-fifth Annual Exhibition by Painter and Sculptor Members and Guest Artists (N134:563)
Jan. 25-Feb. 8, 1953 Annual Water Color Exhibition (N134:564)
Feb. 15-Mar. 1, 1953 Open Exhibition of Oil Paintings (N134:565-568)
Mar. *, 1953 Art of Indonesia
May 3-24, 1953 Members' Exhibition of Smaller Paintings in Oil (N134:569-571)
Nov. 1-14, 1954 The American Artists Professional League, American Art Week (N121:258-259)
Oct. 2-19, 1955 Open Water Color Exhibition
Jan. 8-22 x, 1956 Fifty-eighth Annual Exhibition by Painter and Sculptor Members and Guest Artists (N134:573-575)
June 17-Sept. 7 x, 1956 Members' Summer Exhibition
Sept. 24-Oct. 8 x, 1956 James H. Walsh
Oct. 28-Nov. 10 x, 1956 Small Picture Exhibition by Members and Guests
Nov. 16-30 x, 1956 August Benziger
Dec. 5-22 *, 1956 Fiftieth Anniversary Exhibition of Books of the Year
Jan. 6-27, 1957 Fifty-ninth Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists
Feb. 1-15, 1957 Catherine Lorillard Wolfe Art Club Sixtieth Annual Exhibition (N134:576-577)
Sept. * x, 1957 International Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture
Jan. 10-24 x, 1958 Sixtieth Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists
May 21-31 x, 1958 Water Color and Graphic Arts Exhibition by Members and Non-Members
Oct. 17-31 x, 1958 Twelfth Annual Exhibition of the Photo-Engravers Society
Nov. 22-Dec. 3 x, 1958 Metropolitan Young Artists Show
Jan. 11-26 x, 1959 Sixty-first Annual Exhibition of Painting and Sculpture by Members and Guest Artists